JAN CARLO LIMOCON

PHONE: +63 943 2379096

EMAIL: jancarlo.limocon@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2013 - PRESENT

Web Designer

Produces creative and functional designs for client's websites. Other task responsibilities: Graphics Designing, Web Design Modification and Customization, and Website Front-End Development.

2018 - 2013 (FREELANCE) IT Technical Support Graphics Designer

Web Designer

MAY 2006 - MAY 2007

IT Technical Support
Graphics Designer

In charge in Computer Network and Internet maintenance, upgrade and troubleshooting/Computer Hardware and Software maintenance and upgrade for Internet Cafes, also in charge in Desktop Publishing and Graphics Design.

APRIL 2004 - JULY 2005

IT Technical Support

In charge in Computer Network and Internet maintenance, upgrade and troubleshooting/Computer Hardware and Software maintenance and upgrade for companies and personal users.

EDUCATION

BS in Computer Engineering	1997 - 2002
Secondary Education	1994 - 1997
Primary Education	1989 - 1994



ABOUT ME

Experienced Web Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Strong information technology professional skilled in HTML, CSS, Search Engine Optimization (SEO), PHP, WordPress, Web/Graphics Design and Front-end Development.

SKILLS

HTML		
CSS		
GRAPHICS DESIGN		
UI/UX/WEB DESIGN		
FRONT-END DEVELOPMEN		
WORDPRESS		
PHP		
JAVASCRIPT		